# **Tobias Pristupin**

### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER St. Louis, MO

**1** +1 954-371-7815

🔽 p.tobias@wustl.edu 📘 😭 www.pristu.dev

## Summary\_

Hi, I'm Tobias. I am a self taught programmer from Argentina with 5 years of experience seeking an internship for summer 2021. I have experience in mobile development, programming language theory, robotics, and I am currently learning web development. More information about my projects can be found on my website.

### Education

#### **Washington University in St. Louis**

St. Louis, MO

COMPUTER SCIENCE + MATHEMATICS MAJOR

Aug. 2020 - Present

 Attending on a full scholarship as an Ervin Scholar. Involved in the Association for Computing Machinery (ACM) and the Society of Hispanic Engineers.

## **Cypress Bay High School**

Weston, FL

HIGH SCHOOL

Apr. 2017 - Jul. 2020

- GPA: 5.1, standardized test scores in the 99th percentile. Recipient of the AP Scholar with Distinction Award and the National Hispanic Recognition Award.
- President of the Computer Science Club.

# **Work Experience & Projects**

**Code A Robot** Weston, FL

**TEACHER** Jun. 2019 - Sep. 2019

- Introduced children aged 6-14 to coding. I Taught the basics of Python and JS and interfaced with the real world using robots such as Sphero. Within 3 months 10 students went from no experience to controlling robots through
- Provided one-on-one mentoring to advanced students and taught them intermediate programming concepts. Students achieved a programming level similar to a first year college student.

**Minimal Running** GitHub

**DEVELOPER** 2018-19 • Published Android application with 100+ downloads. Allows user to log their running activities and view statistics on

their progress. Users can use an account to store their data online. Lox Interpreter GitHub

DEVELOPER 2020

Developed an interpreter from scratch in C++ for the Lox Programming language.

# **Volunteering**

#### Association of Computing Machinery (ACM)

Washington University in St.

Louis

• Manage logistics, content, and advertising for ACM events.

**EVENT ORGANIZER** Sep. 2020 - Present

- Developed virtual events for the upcoming year
- **Computer Science Club**

Cypress Bay High School

PRESIDENT

July. 2019 - July. 2020

Directed Competitive Programming team (10 members). Placed 6th at UCF's Programming Tournament (100 teams).

Organized weekly practices (30 members) and taught competitive programming topics to younger students.

#### Skills

**Programming Languages** C++, Java, Python, Dart, Lisp

**Interests** 

Bilingual (English and Spanish), Android Development, Flutter, Arduino, Raspberry Pi, Linux, Interpreters/Com LaTeX, Competitive Programming, Algorithms & Data Structures